A Guide to the Al Gross Papers 1909-2000
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Oversize Materials 1935-96, n.d.
  - Awards, Originals, Articles 1935-96, n.d. (Oversize 21)
    Al Gross Patents (4) - original copies (1952-56)
    Montgomery Ward Blanket Order Form - Citizens Radio Corporation (original)(June 9, 1948)
    Amateur Radio Operator License (original) (November 26, 1935)
    Photocopied images from the Virginia Tech Imagebase (n.d.)
    Photo, Symposium Internacional de Electronica (March 1996)
    Cloth sign, "Presented to Mr. A. Gross by Dundalk C.B. Club" (1980)
    Cloth sign, "Europa Burger Band" (n.d.) Drexel University and IEEE, framed certificate (Fall 1979)
    Letter confirming Al Gross as an IEEE Fellow (December 7, 1981)
    The Cleveland Press Victory Edition (WWII) (August 15, 1945)